

Stephanie Duffieux

ADMINISTRATION OFFICER
GRAPHIC DESIGNER

37 Donnelly Street, Mango Hill QLD 4509

2 0420 579 085

Key Skills

- High level administrative & EA/
 PA support.
- Accounts management.
- Project support.
- Graphic Design.
- Web Design.
- Customer Service.

Technical Proficiency

Platforms

• Windows/Mac

Applications

Advanced Microsoft Office

- Word
- Excel
- PowerPoint
- Outlook

Advanced Adobe Design Suite:

- Photoshop
- InDesign
- Ilustrator
- Wordpress

Summary of Experience:

Enthusiastic bi-lingual (French/English) professional Administration Officer and creative Graphic Designer.

19 years experience in business administration, customer service, office management and general accounts management.

Qualified Graphic Designer with over 4 years experience, specialising in multimedia marketing, digital and print design. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop), Microsoft Office Suite and Wordpress.

Education & Qualifications:

 Foundation & Advanced Skills for Elite Personal Assistants and Executive Assistants Training Course, 2017

Professional Development Training, Brisbane QLD

Diploma in Graphic Design, 2012.

Martin College of Business, Technology & Design, Brisbane QLD

Certificate IV in Graphic Design, 2011.

Martin College of Business, Technology & Design, Brisbane QLD

French Baccalaureate, 2001.

Lycée Laperouse, New-Caledonia

Personal Skills:

- Strong team player and ability to work individually.
- Excellent work ethic and upholding a strict level of confidentiality.
- Excellent computer skills and typing accuracy.
- High level of organisational skills and precise attention to detail.
- Positive, friendly personality.
- Reliable and quick learner, ability to multi task and meet deadlines.
- Diplomacy and sensitivity when working with clients.
- Excellent "can do" attitude towards work.

Work Experience

Executive Assistant / Graphic Designer

2017 - 2019 | Xplore Resources Pty Ltd, Brisbane

Role duties & responsibilities:

Administrative Duties:

- Provide EA/PA support to the CEO whilst upholding a strict level of confidentiality.
- Coordinate executive communications, responding to emails and interfacing with clients on behalf of the CEO.
- Prepare external and internal corporate documents for team members and industry partners.
- Schedule and coordinate meetings and appointments.
- Agenda preparation and minute taking.
- Maintain an organised filing system of paper and electronic documentation.
- Develop and sustain a level of professionalism among staff and clientele.
- Provide high level administration support including diary management, schedules, presentation preparation, creating spreadsheets, registers, word processing.
- Management of administration assistant traineeship program.
- Support the Accounts Manager in processing tasks.
- Undertake ad-hoc administrative tasks at the request of the CEO, Accounts Manager, Deployments Manager and Geology Department.

Graphic Design Duties:

- Manage and process all graphic design tasks including the design of promotional materials and multimedia marketing for the company and business partners.
- Professionally design ASX Announcements and presentations for the Geology Department.
- Design of company brochures and marketing materials for large mining events.
- Design and layout of all content for large mining tender submissions, 300-500 pages, within tight deadlines.
- Website design, development and maintenance for various clients and business partners using Wordpress.
- Logo and brand identity design for various clients and business partners.
- Design and management of social media content for the company.

Customer Account Manager

2015 - 2017 | APN / News Corp, Yandina Qld

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Ensure timely and accurate completion of all administrative duties including account management duties (invoicing, cost accruals and reconciliation)
- Customer order management, ensuring timely and accurate completion of customer's information included in system.
- Communicate with internal and external stakeholders on new and existing products to ensure products / customer needs are met within operational constraints.
- Assist with coordination of transport and publishing requirements.



- Develop an understanding of operational capabilities and contribute to improve customer outcomes.
- Contribute to business improvement and promote development of APN / News Corp Print business systems and process improvement.
- Contribute to a customer service culture throughout the Business based on service excellence.
- Develop dynamic and effective working relationships with external customers, business unit heads, team leaders and team members.
- Ensure clients are receiving the support and assistance required to achieve strategic business goals working with sales and operations.
- Provide support to the sales team and contribute to development and maintenance of a client relationship management strategy.
- Coordinate / manage issues as they arise in relation to customers and communicate with all key stakeholders.
- Work with sales team in providing direction and alternatives on proposal development, assist with presentation and negotiations with key stakeholders.

Administration & Customer Service Officer / Graphic Designer (Bi-Lingual French & English) 2013-2015 | Mail Marketing & Telemarketing Solutions Pty Ltd, Brisbane

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Provide administrative support to the Customer Service department and assist in daily banking, data entry and mail room duties
- Maintain and update client data base.
- Provide assistance in reception and front desk duties.
- Provide a high level of customer service to international clients, English and French.
- Proof reading of various translated documents English to French.
- Assist the arts & production department in designing brochures using Adobe Illustrator, InDesign and Photoshop.

Administration/Customer Service/Accounts Officer, Personal Assistant to CEO 2009-2011 | Pacific Air Cargo Pty Ltd, Brisbane

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Perform all related corporate and administrative duties, working closely with the operations and sales team to ensure accurate correspondence between key stakeholders.
- Perform all bookkeeping duties, accounts receivables / payables, invoicing, reconciliations, quarterly business activity statements, yearly financials, heavy cash handling, weekly payroll and superannuation.
- Ensure all industry legislations, standards and policies governing human resources and management of all related administrative procedures are met.
- Provide personal assistance to the Chief Executive Officer, manage daily schedules, meetings and travel arrangements.
- Manage work in progress, oversee all freight classifications, routing, dispatching and tracing for international air / sea imports, exports of general and dangerous goods.
- Accurately complete all domestic & international documents in accordance with government, bank, customer & freight forwarder requirements.
- Handle all overseas shipments promptly and efficiently.
- Ensure compliance with logistics regulations.
- Prepare custom clearance documentation, airway bills and bills of lading.



- Provide excellent customer service to existing and prospective clients building strong, loyal and trusting relationships.
- Determine and provide clients with accurate shipping charges.

Administration, Customer Service & Freight Officer

2007-2009 | Aircalin, New-Caledonia (International Airline)

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Provide assistance in all related administrative duties.
- Provide excellent customer service to existing and prospective clients.
- Perform all international air freight duties for exports of general and dangerous goods, perishables and live animals
- Ensure all cargo packed and declared according to strict government and international legislations and regulations.
- Liaise directly with international freight forwarders to ensure compliance with logistics regulations.
- Prepare all customs clearance documentation and airway bills.
- Provide prospective clients with accurate airfreight charges.
- Perform daily cash handling and reconciliation duties.

Administration/Customer Service & Freight Officer

2003-2007 | Socatrans International Freight Forwarding Pty Ltd, New-Caledonia

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Provide high level administrative support including account duties, invoicing, preparation of quotes, accounts receivables/payables and maintain an accurate filing system.
- Ensure completion all freight related documentation, whilst coordinating international air and sea freight duties for imports and exports of general and dangerous goods.
- Provide excellent customer service to existing and prospective clients.
- Provide clients with accurate air and sea freight shipping charges.
- Manage daily routing and tracking of all air and sea freight, imports and exports.
- Liaise directly with clients and suppliers.
- Perform daily reception duties, receive inbound and outbound calls.
- Assist in daily bookkeeping and banking duties.
- Provide assistance to the Operations Manager in daily sales and business marketing.

Administration & Customer Service Officer

2000-2003 | Groupama Gan France Insurance, New-Caledonia

- Role duties & responsibilities:
- Perform all reception and front desk customer service duties.
- Provide assistance with invoicing, preparation of quotes and account duties including accounts receivables and payables.
- Handle new client accounts and sales of Car, Home & Contents insurance.



References

Jenny Sykes (Accounts Manager 2017-Current)

Accounts Manager Xplore Resources Pty Ltd

P

12a/2-4 Flinders Parade North Lakes QLD 4509

Mob: 0407 939 125

Mic Folker (Manager from 2016-2017)

Pre-Press, Operations Manager APN / News Corp

54 Pioneer Rd
 Yandina QLD 4561
 (07) 5454 7823 / Mob: 0437 223 066

Sally Hookey (Manager from 2015-2016)

Customer Service Manager APN / News Corp

54 Pioneer RdYandina QLD 45610409 829 899

Theresa Pretenthaler

Customer Service Manager MMTS Pty Ltd

36 Kremzow RdBrendale QLD 4500(07) 3883 6100

Frederic Pierson

Chief Executive Officer Pacific Air Cargo Pty Ltd Socatrans Pty Ltd

20 Harvey Street North Eagle Farm QLD 4009

2 0449 195 131

